workingfromhome.com 2013-06-09

# WorkingFromHome.com Privacy Policy | Working From Home

Last updated 02/05/2013

WorkingFromHome.com (the or our “Web Site”) is owned and operated by Information Services Inc. The following Privacy Policy discloses Information Services Inc’s practices and policies regarding the gathering and dissemination of personal information.

## Personal Information We Collect

If you register with us or if you make a purchase through our Web Site, we may collect certain personal information. That information may include:

  1. your name, user name, address, phone number and email address;
  2. credit card information whenever a purchase is made; and
  3. account preferences.

This information may be collected and may be used for a number of purposes:

  * To establish and maintain a commercial relationship with you and to provide you with products and services. Personal contact and credit card information is required to process your purchases. Account information is retained by us to enable our website to identify you, to allow you to set up and access your account and download files which you have purchased. This information is used only for these purposes and is only retained in transaction records required for internal management and auditing purposes, unless you are informed otherwise or you provide your consent.
  * To understand your needs and preferences. We maintain a record of the products and services you receive from us, and we may ask you for additional information so that we can serve you better.
  * To provide you with information you have requested, and to keep you informed with respect to ongoing changes to our website. Your email address may be used to send you our newsletters and mailings.
  * To develop, enhance or provide new products and services. We may from time to time conduct surveys and research, requesting input from our visitors to help us improve our website, products and services in an effort to serve you better. Your participation in such surveys is voluntary, and in some cases you may have the option to participate anonymously. However, your name, address, email and telephone number may be required to take advantage of bonuses or other benefits which may be available to survey participants, in which case your contact information will only be used for notification and fulfillment purposes.
  * To manage and administer our business. The nature of the Internet is such that it passively and automatically collects certain information about a user’s traffic patterns, which may be linked to their Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. These are unique Internet “addresses” assigned to all Web users by their Internet Service Providers (ISP). Server logs record statistical information, such as visitors’ IP addresses, type of operating systems, time and duration of visit, web pages requested, and identify visitors by categories such as domains and browser types. These statistics are only used on an aggregate basis and will not contain any information that could identify you personally.
  * To meet legal, regulatory, security and processing requirements (such as in response to a court order), and otherwise as permitted or required by law.

If we intend to use personal information for purposes not identified to you or as set out above, these other purposes will be described to you at the time of collection or before using the information. We will not use your information for any other purpose without your consent.

## Cookies

Users also should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of our Internet servers or through the use of “cookies”. Cookies are small text files containing a unique identification number that identifies your browser – but not you – to our servers each time you visit our website. Cookies are not pervasive or invasive programs that enter a user’s system and damage files. They simply tell us which pages of our website are visited and by how many visitors. Cookies cannot, by themselves, disclose the individual identity of any site user, and we never combine information gathered by a cookie with personally identifiable information like your name, telephone number or email address, without your consent.

You should be aware that WorkingFromHome.com cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for the Web Site. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that you may have to have cookies enabled in your browser if you wish to make a purchase on our website, log into your account or download files.

## Third Parties’ Access to Information

Information Services Inc. is not in the business of selling customer information to others. Our customer information is not available for sale to any outside entity except where a sale or transfer of the Web Site or of part or all of Information Services Inc’s business occurs. Customer information is a valuable business asset. If for any reason Information Services Inc. transfers or divests itself of its business assets, our customer information will be transferred as one of those business assets. We may contract with third parties to fulfill certain functions on our behalf, such as providing marketing assistance, analyzing data, preparing and maintaining site content, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These agents may have access to customer information only as required in order to help them perform their functions on our behalf, but they are not allowed to use that information for any other purpose and must keep such information confidential.

We also may work with affiliates, and in some cases we offer services or sell goods and services jointly with these affiliates. When you purchase such goods or services that are provided jointly by WorkingFromHome.com and one of its affiliates, we share our customer information with that affiliate with respect to your purchase.

Site visitors should be aware that WorkingFromHome.com may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through our website. WorkingFromHome.com is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties, and you should check the applicable privacy policy of such party before providing personally identifiable information.

WorkingFromHome.com will release customer information to the appropriate law enforcement, governmental or other authorities if legally required to do so or in Information Services Inc.’s sole discretion in order to reasonably comply with requests from such authorities. WorkingFromHome.com will also release such information if we feel it is necessary in order to protect our rights or the rights of our customers, affiliates, partners or any other party and for purposes of protection from fraud and credit risk.

## External Links

The WorkingFromHome.com website may contains links or references to other websites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply. These sites are not owned or controlled by Information Services Inc and Information Services Inc is not responsible for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information or the privacy practices of other organizations or other websites to which our site may refer visitors or provide links for. When submitting personal information on such other websites, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of those sites.

## Non-Secure Website Areas

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, email address) on non-secure areas of the Web Site, that information can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities may be beyond the control of Information Services Inc however these activities are expressly prohibited by our Terms and Conditions of Use.

## Security

We may store subscriber and password information on our website in a secure manner. We store such information in a manner not accessible to Web browsers, behind firewall and password protection, or offline.

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the personal information under our control. 

Employees, agents and affiliates of WorkingFromHome.com who require access to your personal information in order to fulfill their job or contractual requirements will have access to your personal information to the extent necessary to fulfill such requirements.

## Updating Your Account Information

If you wish to update your personal information, use the ‘Account Settings’ option after logging in to access your account information and make changes online.

## Your Consent

Consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information may be given in various ways. Consent can be express (e.g., orally, electronically or on a form you may sign describing the intended uses and disclosures of personal information) or implied (e.g., when you provide information necessary for a service you have requested, or in some circumstances where notice has been provided to you about our intentions with respect to your personal information and you have not withdrawn your consent for an identified purpose, such as by using an “opt out” option provided). Consent may be given by your authorized representative (such as a legal guardian or a person having a power of attorney). Generally, by providing us with personal information, we will assume that you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such information for the purposes identified or described in this Privacy Policy, if applicable, or as otherwise described at the time of collection. You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of personal information at any time, subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice, however, please note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your personal information, we may no longer be able to provide certain of our products or services.

WorkingFromHome.com does not collect, use or disclose your personal information other than as described in this privacy policy without your consent, unless permitted or required by law. We may be required or permitted under statute or regulation to collect, use or disclose personal information without your consent, for example in response to a court order or subpoena, to comply with local or federal regulations, or to collect a debt owed to us.

## Contacting Us

This website may be subject to the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. This legislation closely regulates the handling of personal information. You can find more information on this Act through the Government of Canada site, www.canada.gc.ca. You may have a right to know what information we have on file about you. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to review your personal information, you can contact us by email at **support@workingfromhome.com**

**ATTENTION: Privacy Officer**

If you are not satisfied with our response to your privacy concerns, you may wish to contact the Privacy Commissioner via http://www.privcom.gc.ca/.

Any dispute arising between the users of WorkingFromHome.com and Information Services Inc. with respect to privacy is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use and this Privacy Policy, and is subject to the laws of the Province of Ontario and of Canada. The foregoing policies are effective as of 02/05/2013. WorkingFromHome.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the policy changes on our website. Site visitors are advised to periodically check this website for such changes.
